Baby.
Come here.
You said
you'd handle everything,
but left it all to Eason in the end.
Sister Hu told Eason to follow me 24/7.
I rehearse every day,
and he has nothing to do.
At least he's not bored now.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's fine, Director.
I actually quite enjoy the process.
Here,
have some more.
Oh no!
Jinxi's head is gone!
What?
Xiao Qi,
you scared us to death.
can you finish your sentences in the future?
This isn't the first time.
It was taken down a couple of days ago.
Could a fan have done it?
That's unlikely.
I've been keeping watch here.
Jin Xi really has all kinds of fans.
It must be some classless person who snuck in at night.
Forget it. We'll just print a new one.
Actually, Jinxi's rehearsal location
among us fans
is not a secret at all.
But we've always followed the rules
and would never do such a thing.
Yeah.
Really?
Of course.
After the theater incident last time,
didn't Sister Hu scold us?
Yeah.
We've tightened our internal discipline.
And look, Jinxi has been rehearsing for so long,
when have we ever sneaked a peek?
Right.
You don't believe us?
Then don't drink our tea.
And don't eat our snacks either.
Don't listen to our music.
Don't listen to the music either.
Don't sit on our chairs.
Don't sit on the chairs either.
Goodbye.
Go.
Why are you so stingy?
Hurry up and go.
Okay.
Sorry, and thank you.
The hospital can't take in any more.
We can only try to find people to adopt them ourselves.
It's fine.
Our theater troupe has so many people.
We won't have to worry about no one adopting them.
Them?
Bai Feixin's place is so cluttered there's no room to step.
The kitten could easily be buried alive.
It's a safety hazard.
What about Jiaoye and Eldest Cousin?
Jiaoye and Eldest Cousin
are perfectly fine when apart.
But...
I told you not to add honey to the pear juice.
I didn't.
Do you think I have no sense of taste?
I made you pear juice,
and I still have to apologize?
I'm not mad about whether you added honey.
I'm mad that you clearly added it,
but lied and said you didn't.
Give it to me if you won't drink it.
Mengtejiao.
If they are together,
it's like a ticking time bomb.
Then the kitten is very likely
to be like the paper cup in their hands.
Absolutely not.
Then Jianshe should be fine, right?
Jianshe lives an exquisite life
and is emotionally stable.
Heying's emotional stability
is built on the foundation of an exquisite life.
Keeping a cat will disrupt his exquisite life.
For instance,
that well-preserved
Liaozhai he's holding.
If it gets a tuft of cat hair on it,
his emotions won't be stable anymore.
Then Xiaoqi should be fine, right?
Xiaoqi is indeed the most ideal candidate.
But her landlord doesn't allow her to keep pets.
Then how about asking them to check with people around them
if they're willing to adopt?
That's all we can do.
I don't have time to ask around about adopting a cat for you.
What cat is up for adoption?
Then help me ask Mr. Wu
if anyone wants to adopt a kitten.
He is asking you
I have a niece.
Ning Jin, I asked my friend for you.
She's been wanting a second cat recently.
Director.
My friend runs a cat cafe.
She says she can take in a new member.
Actually, our colleague is also very interested in your cat.
He often asks me for pictures of the kittens.
I mean Andy.
Ah.
Yeah.
Andy also really likes cats.
You can talk to him.
Mr. Wu said his niece also wants to adopt.
Who told him?
I asked Hu to tell him.
There are so many people interested now.
There aren't enough cats to go around.
Okay.
But they all have to pass my interview
so I can know
if they are qualified adopters.
Good kitty.
Where are you from?
Chengdu.
How many people are in your family?
Three.
How old are you?
I'm 20 this year.
23.
24.
What's your major?
Chinese Language and Literature.
Broadcasting and Hosting.
Do you live alone now?
Alone.
Have you ever had a pet?
I've never had a pet before.
I kept one for three months.
I looked after it for a friend.
If you had three cats,
what would you name them?
Laicai,
and Yuanbao.
If all three cats fell into the water at the same time,
which one would you save first?
I'd save
Laicai.
What about Yuanbao and Xiaobai?
My mom would save them.
How many relationships have you had?
About five.
How long was the longest?
And the shortest?
Seven months at most.
One week at least.
The longest is only seven months.
Then how can you guarantee you'll be responsible for a cat?
I feel like humans can't give me a sense of security,
but cats can.
Because I think cats suit me better.
Wait a minute.
You keep saying how well you dance.
What does dancing have to do with keeping a cat?
But I'm here to audition as a dancer.
Then go prepare a dance routine.
Okay.
Be careful.
So why did you install this?
Last night,
nobody emptied the trash can in our rehearsal room, right?
When I came this morning, there was nothing inside.
I asked the cleaner.
She didn't empty it either.
Does it matter who emptied it?
There was Mr. Heying's delivery box in the trash can,
and Bai Feixin's snack wrappers.
Most importantly,
Jinxi's mask was in it.
You remember all that?
Director,
don't you get it?
It must be that pervert who cut the poster,
pushing his luck to steal Jinxi's trash.
So I bought a surveillance camera.
We have to catch him.
So,
Director,
can this
be reimbursed?
24K ultra-HD 360-degree,
AI facial recognition night vision camera.
I should be able to take this home to monitor my cat.
Director, so it can be reimbursed, right?
Could it be Judy?
Judy?
I don't think so.
Does Jingjing look like one?
Jingjing is pretty honest.
I also think she's quite honest.
Then it must be Watson.
No.
Hello.
Feixin.
Hello, everyone.
Are you Jin Xi's fans?
What are you doing...
Isn't there a weird person recently?
A sasaeng.
No.
It's not like that.
Those people aren't even considered fans.
We fans are very rational.
Those people have psychological problems.
They don't see themselves and Xi
as fans and idols.
Instead, they treat him as their private property.
They objectify him.
It's so scary.
That's really scary.
Well...
You guys carry on.
Alright.
I'll get going now.
Bye.
Feixin.
It's about time I go pick up my brother.
Then we'll go with you to shoot something.
Well...
Sure.
Just keep your distance.
Don't worry.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me
if Jin Xi has finished his rehearsal?
You're his fan, right?
Sorry.
It's not convenient to share his personal schedule.
I'm not his fan.
I'm his...
Anyway.
I have a very important private matter with him.
So could you take me to see him?
It's not very convenient.
Besides, I'm not that close to Jin Xi.
Are you Bai Feixin?
Aren't you his partner?
Don't worry. I'm not a bad person.
Don't think I don't know what kind of person you are.
You're exactly what they call...
that kind of...
I'm warning you.
Stay away from our Xiyin Theatre Troupe and Jin Xi.
This is just a warning.
If there's a next time, I won't be polite.
No.
I...
Feixin,
are you okay?
Are you okay?
Here,
have some water.
Why are you here?
Of course I had to come.
I was only on a business trip for two days and such a big thing happened.
Are you okay?
Where are you hurt?
She...
The one who got hurt is me.
Fortunately, I brought pepper spray with me,
so nothing happened.
Eason, you really...
You didn't explain it to me clearly.
I heard that these past two days,
there are two or three fans making trouble in the troupe.
Thank goodness nothing major happened.
I apologize to everyone here.
I'm sorry.
It's not just a matter of the past two or three days.
Every day since we started rehearsing,
there have been three weird fans
blocking the door.
I suggest you kick them out.
Those three haven't done anything terrible.
They haven't even entered the building.
Where else can we chase them to?
Who knows if they cut the poster?
They also steal garbage.
Yeah.
Bai Feixin and Jin Xi acted together,
and they were attacked.
You have quite a good temper.
If it were me,
I'd call the cops on him
so he wouldn't come back.
Come back?
No way.
Didn't you know?
These toxic solo fans
hate it when couples are shipped.
Hitting you is getting off lightly.
Be careful, they might stalk you
and splash paint on your house.
So,
you should be responsible for the fans' behavior.
I assure everyone,
this kind of thing will absolutely not happen again.
We'll strengthen security.
Then the past incidents,
are just written off like that?
What else do you want us to do?
Brother Jianshe is right.
I'll take responsibility.
Xiao Qi.
I'll reimburse you for the cameras you bought.
Buy a few more.
And I'll reprint the torn posters.
Sister Hu.
I'll pay for the extra security fees
out of my income.
Alright.
That's the end of it.
Let's go.
Manager.
Sister.
Do you have a minute?
We have something very important to tell you.
Go ahead.
The person who attacked Bai Feixin
is definitely not from the official fan club.
But they came prepared.
You can't be on guard forever.
What do you mean?
Sister, we found out
that someone has been secretly selling Jinxi's schedule.
I have screenshots here.
Do you know who is selling the schedule?
We don't know.
His identity is confidential.
But we have already emphasized
to all the fans in the fan club
not to buy schedules from him anymore.
To protect our brother,
we stayed up all night to create a 5,000-word
safety investigation report on Jin Xi.
Look, sister.
As expected of a top student.
Producer: Zhang Yawei
Alright.
Shuai, will this work?
First of all, congratulations on making it to the second round of interviews.
Your profile is very complete.
I have no further questions on my end.
Do you have any questions for me?
We will sign a formal adoption agreement, right?
Of course.
Then I have no questions.
Andy Liu.
I will notify you as soon as there is any news.
I haven't seen you around.
What are you here for?
I'm here for the second round of interviews.
Second round of interviews?
Is our theater troupe hiring new people?
How come I didn't know about this?
Who told you to come?
The director.
Boss Wu.
You mean Uncle Wu?
Uncle Wu?
Calling him so affectionately?
Because he is my uncle.
I'm his own niece.
So you have connections.
Which play are you auditioning for?
Which role?
I...
What did you major in before?
How old are you, and what school do you go to?
How old are you really?
Are you a musical theater major?
Feixin.
Don't worry too much.
This might not have anything to do with you.
Hello.
Lin Yimin.
So,
did your mom tell you
how many kittens you can keep?
My mom said I can keep three.
You said before
that you raised chicks and turtles.
So are they still alive?
Well, they were alive.
It's just that...
The chick grew wings
and flew out the window.
The turtle sneaked out of the fish tank,
and my dad didn't find it until three months later.
It turned into a dried turtle.
But that was back in elementary school.
I will be responsible for these three lives in the future.
Okay, I see.
Do you have any other questions for me?
I really like Jin Xi.
Miss,
can you help me get a photo with her later?
Thank you.
Sister Hu.
What's so mysterious
that you didn't even invite Eason?
What's wrong?
Ever since Bai Feixin was attacked last time,
I hired a professional to investigate.
I wouldn't have known if I hadn't investigated.
You are practically living in a nightmare.
Did you know?
In our company,
someone is selling your itinerary information at a high price.
No way.
Yes.
Look.
ID information is 20 each,
flight information is 50 each,
and accommodation information is 100 each.
The monthly itinerary,
direct from the studio, is 2,000.
Isn't this money too easy to make?
It took me a lot of effort to buy this yesterday.
Is it really someone from our studio?
I've been planning this for a long time.
The itinerary they each received is the same,
but I made different marks on them.
We'll know who it is once we open it.
Look.
Did you bring the money?
This is too expensive.
Is 2,500 really that expensive?
What are you guys doing?
Don't run!
Stop right there!
Who is this guy?
You won't tell me?
If you don't, I'll tell Sister Hu everything about you.
We don't know who he is either.
He told us to call him Brother Tian.
What's wrong, Sister?
Why meet here?
How long have you been with me?
About three years.
In our company.
You are actually the person I trust the most.
Ever since I marked the itineraries
and narrowed down the scope.
Unfortunately,
this suspect is not in the Xiyin Troupe,
but in our company.
So,
can I still continue to trust you?
Sister.
I swear,
I am completely loyal to you and Brother Jinxi.
I would absolutely never do anything to betray you guys.
Absolutely not.
Good.
Then follow me
and let's root out this person selling the itineraries.
Okay.
After careful consideration,
you are the final adopter of the three kittens.
Thank you so much.
We can start signing the agreement now.
Your name is...
Zhang Naitian.
Yes.
Andy is just my English name.
Excuse me.
Yes.
The usual price.
See you at the usual place tonight.
We don't know who he is either.
He told us to call him Brother Tian.
Let's leave it at that for now.
Let's continue.
Sorry.
Something just came up.
Let's sign it next time.
Didn't we already...
Why did you ask me to meet you on the roof?
I'm not like you.
I don't need to hide in the shadows.
I don't know what you mean.
Director Ning Jin
saw you selling his information with her own eyes.
She didn't see your face clearly,
but she knows the fans call you Brother Tian.
Zhang Naitian.
Isn't that you?
Besides, you have a subconscious habit
that you can't hide at all.
You like to slap your thigh.
Give me a chance.
How can I give you a chance?
I didn't have a choice before.
Now I want to be a good person.
Fine.
Go ask Sister Hu.
See if she agrees.
Don't come any closer.
My name is not Andy.
I don't want to get caught.
Are you crazy?
You are insane.
Why are you taking a hostage?
I'm not sending you to the police.
You're not calling the police?
I came to inform you
that you are fired.
Leave now.
Don't let me see you again.
I...
Thank you, Ms. Hu.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I doubted you before.
I am absolutely loyal to you and Jinxi.
So are we to you.
By the way,
I recently wrote a new song.
Can you listen to it?
It's a folk song.
I...
Hello?
Okay.
Your phone didn't light up.
Sister,
you...
Wait for me.
One, two, three.
Look.
Mom, you took a great photo.
Thank you guys.
Keep it down.
They are so small.
So cute.
They will grow up quickly,
just like you.
I will play with them every day
and take good care of them.
Right, the kittens don't have names yet.
Jinxi,
can you name them?
How about
Makuna, Matata, and Simba?
No.
That's a mouthful.
What do you think?
Their mom's name is Jinzi.
So they should be called Jin Damao, Jin Ermao, and Jin Xiaomao.
Good thing you're a director,
not a screenwriter.
The most important thing in naming animals is
being easy to remember
and catchy.
Indeed.
You bickering looks just like my dad and mom.
How is it?
Are you happy now?
Andy was fired for leaking the itinerary.
Looking at it now, it's not a bad thing.
Minmin is so caring.
Why wasn't she your first choice?
Because during the second interview,
I found out she's your fan.
I was worried her motives were impure,
so I didn't choose her.
But later I asked Lao Wu to do a background check on her.
Although she is your fan,
she did a lot of research for the adoption.
She is sincere.
She's really interesting.
She named the cats Axi, Ajin, and Eason.
Naming them after the people who took care of them,
she's a gentle kid.
Then Eason is too pitiful.
It sounds like he's not from the same litter as the other two.
I feel empty inside.
Do you think we look like
parents whose children have married off?
Who's a couple with you?
What do you want to do?
Nothing.
This is too unfair.
- A-Z0518.
- How is it unfair?
But every time you kiss me, I don't hide.
- Nai A-Z0518.
- You hide when I kiss you.
Not hiding is your business.
Hiding is mine.
Let's go.
I'm here to support you.
Let me say this again.
They will also come to this stream to ask Feixin for advice!
A normal friendship.
They will also come to this stream to ask Feixin for advice! Indeed, in this industry,
they will also come to this stream to ask Feixin for advice!
Super Brain: Good evening, Feixin. Here to watch you talk about falling in love on set.
On me, Feixin.
Jasmine Milk Green: Feixin is right.
Mortal: Feixin's analysis makes me feel that mixing work and feelings
Mortal: Feixin's analysis is so accurate. It is very unprofessional.
Mortal: Feixin's analysis is really accurate.
Mortal: Feixin's analysis is really... I have to go to an industry party now.
Alright, friends,
see you next time. Bye.
What industry party?
Just an industry party between the two of us.
No drinking.
You are going into the black box tomorrow.
Drink this.
When did you start live streaming?
I've been doing it for quite a while.
Just giving it a try.
Having a backup plan.
What kind of content do you stream?
Relationship advice.
You?
Relationship advice?
What's wrong?
Experience makes you an expert, understand?
Let me tell you.
If I'm walking on the street right now
and a man walks toward me,
I can tell at a glance if he's a good guy
or a jerk.
Bro,
your single will be released online next week.
It's set.
Bro, what's wrong with you?
If only love
could be like releasing a single,
set just like that.
How great that would be.
You're writing a song?
This song
is inspired by the emotional journey of a friend of mine.
Would you like to hear it?
Bro,
Are you going to co-create with me, bro?
I'll listen.
You talk, I'm listening.
I have time.
My friend and her...
Not only is there an unspoken connection,
but also many secrets.
Not only do they have an unspoken connection,
they also have many secrets.
The sparks flying between them.
She refuses to admit it,
won't even talk about it,
but hasn't denied it.
The sparks that flew,
she neither admits nor denies.
Why is it exactly?
She refuses to look me in the eyes,
or embrace love.
Why exactly
is it?
She refuses to look him in the eyes,
nor is she willing
to embrace
love.
Bro.
I...
Overall, after hearing the lyrics,
I feel
they aren't bold and direct enough.
What do you mean by bold and direct?
You mean
saying 'I love you' directly?
Yes.
Just say it.
No matter how fancy the words are,
they can't match a simple confession.
I got it.
I know how to write the chorus.
Bro.
A thousand words can't compare to
'I love you'.
I understand.
Thank you.
Bro,
no more collaborations.